How much? 100€?

(English) I can eat glass and it doesn't hurt me.
(Greek) Μπορώ να φάω σπασμένα γυαλιά χωρίς να πάθω τίποτα.
(Hungarian) Meg tudom enni az üveget, nem lesz tőle bajom.
(Icelandic) Ég get etið gler án þess að meiða mig.
(Polish) Mogę jeść szkło i mi nie szkodzi.
(Russian) Я могу есть стекло, оно мне не вредит.
(Arabic): أنا قادر على أكل الزجاج و هذا لا يؤلمني. 
(Hebrew): אני יכול לאכול זכוכית וזה לא מזיק לי.
(Chinese) 我能吞下玻璃而不伤身体。
(Japanese) 私はガラスを食べられます。それは私を傷つけません。
(Hindi) मैं काँच खा सकता हूँ और मुझे उससे कोई चोट नहीं पहुंचती.
